A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1940-1946 FA758
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1941
  - England, 1941; 1941/401
    - Britain - Health - Jameson, Sir Wilson, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1537)
    - Britain - (I-P), 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1538)
    - Britain - (R-Z), 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1539)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1941; 1941/401.A
      - Britain, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1540)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/401.E
      - Britain, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1540)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/401.R
      - Britain, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1540)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1941; 1941/401.S
      - Britain, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1540)
  - Scotland, 1941; 1941/405
    - Scotland, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1540)
  - Australia, 1941; 1941/410
    - Australia, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1541)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/410.E
      - Australia, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1541)
    - Australia - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/410.R
      - Australia, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1541)
  - New Zealand, 1941; 1941/418
    - New Zealand, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1541)
  - Fiji, 1941; 1941/419
    - Fiji, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1541)
    - Fiji - Nursing, 1941; 1941/419.C
      - Fiji, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1541)
  - Caribbean Region, 1941; 1941/420
    - Caribbean Region, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1541)
  - Guyana, 1941; 1941/423
    - Guyana - Tuberculosis, 1941; 1941/423.T
      - British Guiana, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1541)
  - Belize, 1941; 1941/425
    - British Honduras, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1541)
    - Belize - Yellow Fever, 1941; 1941/425.O
      - British Honduras, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1541)
  - Canada, 1941; 1941/427
    - Canada - (A-K), 1941 (Box 221, Folder 1542)
    - Canada - (L-Z), 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1543)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1941; 1941/427.A
      - Canada, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1544)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1941; 1941/427.C
      - Canada, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1544)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/427.E
      - Canada, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1544)
    - Canada - Health Services, 1941; 1941/427.K
      - NEW Fox, Leon A. "Sanitary Survey of Newfoundland", 1941 (Box 561, Folder 3815)
    - Canada - Public Health Education, 1941; 1941/427.L
      - Canada, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1544)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/427.R
      - Canada - (A-L), 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1545)
      - Canada - Libraries: Reports, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1546)
      - Canada - (N-Z), 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1547)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, 1941; 1941/427.S
      - Canada, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1548)
  - Bermuda, 1941; 1941/430
    - Bermuda, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1549)
  - West Indies, 1941; 1941/431
    West Indies
    - British Antilles, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1549)
  - Bahamas, 1941; 1941/433
    Bahamas
    - Bahamas, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1549)
  - Jamaica, 1941; 1941/437
    - Jamaica, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1549)
  - Leeward Islands, 1941; 1941/439
    Leeward Islands
    - Leeward Islands - Malaria, 1941; 1941/439.I
      - Antigua, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1549)
  - Trinidad, 1941; 1941/451
    - Trinidad, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1549)
  - St. Lucia, 1941; 1941/457
    Saint Lucia
    - St. Lucia - Public Health Education, 1941; 1941/457.L
      - St. Lucia, 1941 (Box 222, Folder 1549)
  - India, 1941; 1941/464
    - India - Administration, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1550)
    - India - (A-I), 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1551)
    - India - (I-Z), 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1552)
    - India - Nursing, 1941; 1941/464.C
      - India, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1552)
      - TEN-1 Tennant, Mary Elizabeth "Summary of Impressions of Nursing in India", 1941 (Box 561, Folder 3816)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/464.E
      - India, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1553)
    - India - Public Health Education, 1941; 1941/464.L
      - India, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1553)
    - India - Yellow Fever, 1941; 1941/464.O
      - India, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1553)
    - India (Mysore), 1941; 1941/464.1
      - Mysore, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1553)
  - Iraq, 1941; 1941/470
    - Iraq - Malaria, 1941; 1941/470.I
      - Iraq, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1553)
  - Africa, 1941; 1941/475
    - Africa, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1554)
    - Africa - Social Sciences, 1941; 1941/475.S
      - Africa, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1554)
  - East Africa Region, 1941; 1941/477
    Africa, East
    - East Africa Region -Yellow Fever, 1941; 1941/477.O
      - MOM-1 Mombasa "Extract From the Annual Report of the Port Health Officer for Mombasa", 1941 (Box 561, Folder 3817)
  - North Africa Region, 1941; 1941/485
    - Egypt, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1554)
  - West Africa, 1941; 1941/495
    Africa, West
    - West Africa - Yellow Fever, 1941; 1941/495.O
      - Guinea, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1554)
  - France, 1941; 1941/500
    - France - (A-M), 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1555)
    - France - (N-Z), 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1556)
    - France - Medical Sciences, 1941; 1941/500.A
      - France, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1556)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/500.E
      - France, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1556)
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/500.R
      - France, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1556)
  - Vietnam (Indo-China), 1941; 1941/509
    - Indo-China, 1941 (Box 223, Folder 1556)
  - China, 1941; 1941/601
    - China - Administration, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1557)
    - China - (A-Z), 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1558)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1941; 1941/601.A
      - China, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1559)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/601.E
      - China, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1559)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/601.R
      - China, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1559)
  - Japan, 1941; 1941/609
    - Japan, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1560)
  - Thailand, 1941; 1941/617
    - Thailand, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1560)
  - Holland (Netherlands), 1941; 1941/650
    - Netherlands, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1560)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1560)
  - Europe, 1941; 1941/700
    - Europe, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1560)
  - Austria, 1941; 1941/705
    - Austria, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1560)
  - Belgium, 1941; 1941/707
    - Belgium, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1560)
    - Belgium - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/707.E
      - Belgium, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1560)
  - Zaire, 1941; 1941/709
    - Zaire, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1561)
  - Yugoslavia, 1941; 1941/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1561)
  - Bulgaria, 1941; 1941/711
    - Bulgaria, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1561)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1941; 1941/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1561)
  - Denmark, 1941; 1941/713
    - Denmark, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1561)
  - Estonia, 1941; 1941/714
    Estonia
    - Estonia, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1561)
  - Germany, 1941; 1941/717
    - Germany, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 1561)
  - Hungary, 1941; 1941/750
    - Hungary, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1562)
  - Italy, 1941; 1941/751
    - Italy, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1563)
  - Norway, 1941; 1941/767
    - Norway, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1563)
  - Iran, 1941; 1941/771
    Iran
    - Iran, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1564)
  - Portugal, 1941; 1941/773
    Portugal
    - Portugal, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1564)
    - Portugal - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/773.E
      - Portugal, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1564)
  - Romania, 1941; 1941/783
    - Romania, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1564)
  - U.S.S.R., 1941; 1941/785
    - U.S.S.R., 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1564)
  - Finland, 1941; 1941/787
    - Finland, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1564)
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/787.E
      - Finland, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1564)
  - Poland, 1941; 1941/789
    - Poland, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1565)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/789.E
      - Poland, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1565)
  - Sweden, 1941; 1941/800
    - Sweden, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1565)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/800.E
      - Sweden, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1565)
  - Switzerland, 1941; 1941/803
    - Switzerland, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1565)
  - Lebanon, 1941; 1941/833
    Lebanon
    - Lebanon, 1941 (Box 225, Folder 1565)
- General Correspondence, 1942
  - International, 1942; 1942/100
    - (A-E), 1942 (Box 225, Folder 1566)
    - (F), 1942 (Box 225, Folder 1567)
    - (L), 1942 (Box 226, Folder 1568)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1942 (Box 226, Folder 1569)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1942 (Box 226, Folder 1570)
    - F-I, 1942 (Box 226, Folder 1571)
    - J-K, 1942 (Box 226, Folder 1572)
    - League of Nations, 1942 (Box 226, Folder 1573)
    - (M-N) - Nutrition Studies, 1942 (Box 226, Folder 1574)
    - Nutrition Studies, 1942 (Box 227, Folder 1575)
    - O'Brien, Daniel P., 1942 (Box 227, Folder 1576)
    - (P-Q), 1942 (Box 227, Folder 1577)
    - (R-T), 1942 (Box 227, Folder 1578)
    - (T-W), 1942 (Box 227, Folder 1579)
    - (W-Z), 1942 (Box 227, Folder 1580)
    - International - Nursing, 1942; 1942/100.C
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1942 (Box 227, Folder 1580)
    - International - Malaria, 1942; 1942/100.I
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1942 (Box 227, Folder 1580)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1942; 1942/100.O
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1942 (Box 227, Folder 1580)
  - International - Applications for Employment, 1942; 1942/101
    - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1942 (Box 227, Folder 1580)
  - United States, 1942; 1942/200
    - United States - (A-Am), 1942 (Box 228, Folder 1581)
    - United States - (Amer), 1942 (Box 228, Folder 1582)
    - United States - (Amer), 1942 (Box 228, Folder 1583)
    - United States - (An-Az), 1942 (Box 228, Folder 1584)
    - United States - (B), 1942 (Box 228, Folder 1585)
    - United States - (C-Ce), 1942 (Box 228, Folder 1586)
    - United States - (Co), 1942 (Box 229, Folder 1587)
    - United States - (Co), 1942 (Box 229, Folder 1588)
    - United States - (Co-E), 1942 (Box 229, Folder 1589)
    - United States - (F-Fo), 1942 (Box 229, Folder 1590)
    - United States - Foundation for the Study of Cycles, 1942 (Box 229, Folder 1591)
    - United States - (Fo-Ha), 1942 (Box 229, Folder 1592)
    - United States - Harvard - (A-D), 1942 (Box 229, Folder 1593)
    - United States - Harvard - (E-Si), 1942 (Box 230, Folder 1594)
    - United States - Harvard - (Si-Z), 1942 (Box 230, Folder 1595)
    - United States - (He-Hg), 1942 (Box 230, Folder 1596)
    - United States - (I-In), 1942 (Box 230, Folder 1597)
    - United States - (In), 1942 (Box 230, Folder 1598)
    - United States - (In-K), 1942 (Box 230, Folder 1599)
    - United States - (L-Mac), 1942 (Box 231, Folder 1600)
    - United States - (Ma-Me), 1942 (Box 231, Folder 1601)
    - United States - (Mi-My), 1942 (Box 231, Folder 1602)
    - United States - (N-Ne), 1942 (Box 231, Folder 1603)
    - United States - (Ne-Nz), 1942 (Box 231, Folder 1604)
    - United States - (O-Pa), 1942 (Box 231, Folder 1605)
    - United States - (Pe-Re), 1942 (Box 232, Folder 1606)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (A-K), 1942 (Box 232, Folder 1607)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (L-Z), 1942 (Box 232, Folder 1608)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (Re-Se), 1942 (Box 232, Folder 1609)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (Si), 1942 (Box 232, Folder 1610)
    - United States -(T-U.S. Navy), 1942 (Box 232, Folder 1611)
    - United States -(T-U.S. Navy), 1942 (Box 232, Folder 1611)
    - United States - (U.S. - Public Health Service - State), 1942 (Box 233, Folder 1612)
    - United States - (U.S. - Treasury - Wa), 1942 (Box 233, Folder 1613)
    - United States - (We-Z), 1942 (Box 233, Folder 1614)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1942; 1942/200.A
      - United States, 1942 (Box 233, Folder 1615-1616)
    - United States - Nursing, 1942; 1942/200.C
      - United States, 1942 (Box 233, Folder 1617)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/200.E
      - United States, 1942 (Box 233, Folder 1617)
    - United States - Declinations, 1942; 1942/200.F
      - United States, 1942 (Box 233, Folder 1617)
    - United States - Public Health Education, 1942; 1942/200.L
      - United States, 1942 (Box 233, Folder 1617)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1942; 1942/200.R
      - United States (A-L), 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1618)
      - United States, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1619)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1942; 1942/200.S
      - United States, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1619)
  - Alabama, 1942; 1942/201
    - Alabama, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1620)
  - Arkansas, 1942; 1942/204
    - Arkansas, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1620)
  - California, 1942; 1942/205
    - California, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1620)
    - California - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1942; 1942/205.D
      - California, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1620)
    - California - Humanities and Arts, 1942; 1942/205.R
      - California, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1620)
  - Panama Canal Zone, 1942; 1942/206
    - Panama Canal Zone - Malaria, 1942; 1942/206.I
      - Canal Zone, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1621)
  - Colorado, 1942; 1942/207
    - Colorado - Social Sciences, 1942; 1942/207.S
      - Colorado, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1621)
  - Connecticut, 1942; 1942/208
    - Connecticut, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1621)
  - Florida, 1942; 1942/211
    - Florida, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1621)
    - Florida - Yellow Fever, 1942; 1942/211.O
      - Florida, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1621)
  - Georgia, 1942; 1942/212
    - Georgia, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1622)
  - Hawaii, 1942; 1942/214
    Hawaii
    - Hawaii, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1622)
  - Illinois, 1942; 1942/216
    - Illinois, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1622)
  - Kansas, 1942; 1942/219
    - Kansas, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1622)
  - Kentucky, 1942; 1942/220
    - Kentucky, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1622)
    - Kentucky - Public Health Education, 1942; 1942/220.L
      - Kentucky, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1622)
  - Maine, 1942; 1942/222
    Maine
    - Maine, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1622)
  - Maryland, 1942; 1942/223
    - Maryland, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1623)
  - Massachusetts, 1942; 1942/224
    - Massachusetts, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1623)
  - Mississippi, 1942; 1942/227
    - Mississippi, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1623)
  - Missouri, 1942; 1942/228
    - Missouri, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1623)
  - Montana, 1942; 1942/229
    - Montana, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1623)
  - New Hampshire, 1942; 1942/232
    - New Hampshire, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 1623)
  - New Mexico, 1942; 1942/234
    - New Mexico - Public Health Education, 1942; 1942/234.L
      - New Mexico, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1624)
  - North Carolina, 1942; 1942/236
    - North Carolina, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1624)
    - North Carolina - Cooperative Nutrition Study, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1625)
  - Ohio, 1942; 1942/238
    - Ohio, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1626)
  - Pennsylvania, 1942; 1942/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1626)
    - Pennsylvania - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1942; 1942/241.D
      - Pennsylvania, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1626)
    - Pennsylvania - Humanities and Arts, 1942; 1942/241.R
      - Pennsylvania, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1626)
  - Philippines, 1942; 1942/242
    - Philippines, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1626)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/242.E
      - Philippines, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1626)
  - Rhode Island, 1942; 1942/244
    - Rhode Island, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1626)
  - South Carolina, 1942; 1942/246
    - South Carolina, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1626)
  - Tennessee, 1942; 1942/248
    - Tennessee, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1627)
    - Tennessee - Hookworm, 1942; 1942/248.H
      - Tennessee, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1627)
  - Vermont, 1942; 1942/251
    Vermont
    - Vermont, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1627)
  - Virginia, 1942; 1942/252
    - Virginia, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1628)
  - Washington, 1942; 1942/253
    - Washington, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1628)
  - Wisconsin, 1942; 1942/255
    - Wisconsin, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1628)
  - Virgin Islands, 1942; 1942/257
    - Virgin Islands, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1628)
    - Virgin Islands - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/257.E
      - Virgin Islands, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1628)
  - South America, 1942; 1942/300
    - South America - Administration, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1629)
    - South America - Administration, 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1630)
    - South America - (A-Z), 1942 (Box 235, Folder 1631)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1942; 1942/300.A
      - South America, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1632)
    - South America - Nursing, 1942; 1942/300.C
      - South America, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1632)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1942; 1942/300.D
      - South America, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1632)
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/300.E
      - South America, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1632)
    - South America - Social Sciences, 1942; 1942/300.S
      - South America, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1632)
  - Argentina, 1942; 1942/301
    - Argentina - (A-L), 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1633)
    - Argentina - (M-Z), 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1634)
    - Argentina - Nursing, 1942; 1942/301.C
      - Argentina, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1635)
  - Bolivia, 1942; 1942/303
    - Bolivia, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1635)
    - Bolivia - Nursing, 1942; 1942/303.C
      - Bolivia, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1635)
  - Brazil, 1942; 1942/305
    - Brazil, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1636)
    - Brazil - Nursing, 1942; 1942/305.C
      - Brazil - Nursing, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1637)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1942; 1942/305.D
      - Brazil, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1638)
    - Brazil - Yellow Fever, 1942; 1942/305.O
      - Brazil, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1638)
    - Brazil - Humanities and Arts, 1942; 1942/305.R
      - Brazil, 1942 (Box 236, Folder 1638)
  - Chile, 1942; 1942/309
    - Chile, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1639)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/309.E
      - Chile, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1639)
    - Chile - Respiratory Diseases, 1942; 1942/309.M
      - Chile, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1639)
  - Colombia, 1942; 1942/311
    - Colombia, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1639)
  - Costa Rica, 1942; 1942/313
    - Costa Rica, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1639)
    - Costa Rica - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1942; 1942/313.D
      - Costa Rica, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1639)
  - Cuba, 1942; 1942/315
    - Cuba, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1640)
    - Cuba - Nursing, 1942; 1942/315.C
      - Cuba, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1640)
    - Cuba - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/315.E
      - Cuba, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1640)
  - Ecuador, 1942; 1942/317
    - Ecuador, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1641)
    - Ecuador - Humanities and Arts, 1942; 1942/317.R
      - Ecuador, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1641)
  - Guatemala, 1942; 1942/319
    - Guatemala, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1641)
    - Guatemala - Malaria, 1942; 1942/319.I
      - Guatemala, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1641)
  - Mexico, 1942; 1942/323
    - Mexico, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1641)
    - Mexico - (A-Z), 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1642)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/323.E
      - Mexico, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1643)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1942; 1942/323.R
      - Mexico, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1643)
    - Mexico - Social Sciences, 1942; 1942/323.S
      - Mexico, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1643)
  - Nicaragua, 1942; 1942/325
    - Nicaragua, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1643)
    - Nicaragua - Malaria, 1942; 1942/325.I
      - Nicaragua, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1643)
  - Panama, 1942; 1942/327
    - Panama, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1643)
    - Panama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/327.E
      - Panama, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1643)
    - Panama - Malaria, 1942; 1942/327.I
      - Panama, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1643)
    - Panama - Public Health Education, 1942; 1942/327.L
      - Panama, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1643)
  - Paraguay, 1942; 1942/329
    - Paraguay, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1643)
    - Paraguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1942; 1942/329.D
      - Paraguay, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1643)
    - Paraguay - Malaria, 1942; 1942/329.I
      - Paraguay, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1643)
  - Peru, 1942; 1942/331
    - Peru, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1644)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1942; 1942/331.D
      - Peru, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1644)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/331.E
      - Peru, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1644)
  - El Salvador, 1942; 1942/333
    - El Salvador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/333.E
      - El Salvador, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1644)
  - Dominican Republic, 1942; 1942/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1644)
  - Uruguay, 1942; 1942/337
    - Uruguay, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1644)
    - Uruguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/337.E
      - Uruguay, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1644)
  - Venezuela, 1942; 1942/339
    - Venezuela, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1645)
    - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1942; 1942/339.D
      - Venezuela, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1645)
    - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/339.E
      - Venezuela, 1942 (Box 237, Folder 1645)
  - Great Britain, 1942; 1942/400
    - Britain, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1646)
  - England, 1942; 1942/401
    - England - (A-K), 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1646)
    - England - (L-N), 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1647)
    - England - (O-Z), 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1648)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1942; 1942/401.A
      - England, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1648)
    - England - Public Health Education, 1942; 1942/401.L
      - England, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1648)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1942; 1942/401.R
      - England, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1648)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1942; 1942/401.S
      - England, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1648)
  - Scotland, 1942; 1942/405
    - Scotland, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1649)
  - Australia, 1942; 1942/410
    - Australia, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1649)
  - Cook Islands, 1942; 1942/417
    Cook Islands
    - Cook Islands, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1649)
  - New Zealand, 1942; 1942/418
    - New Zealand, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1649)
    - New Zealand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/418.E
      - New Zealand, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1649)
  - Fiji, 1942; 1942/419
    - Fiji - Malaria, 1942; 1942/419.I
      - Fiji, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1649)
  - Caribbean Region, 1942; 1942/420
    - Caribbean Region, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1649)
  - Honduras, 1942; 1942/425
    Honduras
    - Honduras - Malaria, 1942; 1942/425.I
      - Honduras, 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1650)
  - Canada, 1942; 1942/427
    - Canada (A-N), 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1650)
    - Canada (O-Z), 1942 (Box 238, Folder 1651)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1942; 1942/427.A
      - Canada, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1652)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1942; 1942/427.C
      - Canada, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1652)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1942; 1942/427.E
      - Canada, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1652)
    - Canada - Public Health Education, 1942; 1942/427.L
      - Canada, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1652)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1942; 1942/427.R
      - Canada - (A-F), 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1653)
      - Canada - (G-R), 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1654)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, 1942; 1942/427.S
      - Canada, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1655)
  - Bermuda, 1942; 1942/430
    - Bermuda, 1942 (Box 239, Folder 1656)